Md Mainul Islam Sazib

House: 62/1, West Malibagh, Dhaka 1217 Email: mainul.bd996@gmail.com Facebook Profile: mdmainul.bd Tel.: +8801717503890



CAREER OBJECTIVE:

To ensure a better place where I can utilize my knowledge and experience to build up my career and to make use of my interpersonal skills to achieve goals of an Organization that focuses on customer satisfaction and customer experience.

EXPERIENCE:

• Former HR Executive

November, 2019 to August, 2021

Former Executive (PR & Brand) August, 2018 to October, 2019 Excellence Bangladesh

EDUCATION:

MBA

Year: 2022

Major: Human Resource Management (HRM) Institute: Stamford University Bangladesh

Grade: Appeared

• BBA

Year: 2018 to 2021

Major: Human Resource Management (HRM) Institute: Stamford University Bangladesh

Grade: CGPA 3.49 (out of 4.00)

• HSC

Year: 2016

Institute: Barguna Govt. College, Barguna

Board: Barisal Group: Science

Grade: GPA 4.17 (out of 5.00)

• SSC

Year: 2014

Institute: Barguna Zilla School, Barguna

Board: Barisal Group: Science

Grade: GPA 5.00 (out of 5.00)

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Father's Name : Md Abdul Rab Mia

Mother's Name : Mst. Nasima Begum

Date of birth : 21 November, 1999

Nationality : Bangladeshi
Marital Status : Single
Height : 5.3 feet
Blood Group : B+ (positive)

Permanent Address : sazib bhabon, College Road, Barguna sadar, Barguna-8700

EXTRA CURRICULAM ACTIVITIES:

- Member of ISSUP International Society of Substance Use Professionals March, 2022 to Present
- President of Stamford Anti- Drug Forum August, 2021 to Present
- Event Coordinator of Hult Prize, Stamford University Bangladesh June, 2021 to Present
- Publication Secretary of Stamford Business Forum October, 2018 to Present
- Former Organizing Secretary of Stamford Anti- Drug Forum November, 2020 to July, 2021
- Former General Secretary, Barguna Sadar SAP Bangladesh
 2013 to 2015

LANGUAGE AND PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- Language: Mother tongue Bangla. Fluent in Bangla and Full working knowledge in English.
- Customer Service skills: Problem solving, Written and spoken communication, Attention to detail.
- **Technical Skills**: Proficient with Microsoft Office-(Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook), Data entry skills, Graphics Design and Strong typing skills.

TRAININGS & WORKSHOPS:

- Participate of 3rd Global Forum for Youth Leaders on Drug Use Prevention (GOFORTH) in 12-16 may, 2022.
- Participate of Freelancer to Entrepreneur: The shift in mindset by BACCO in 28th Jan 07th Feb, 2022.
- Participate of Career Retention Grooming Session Think Outside The Box Season-3 By Futurizers Bangladesh in 27th July, 2019.
- Participate of Career Development Training Program "Skills & Learning" By HR perception in 18th May, 2019.
- Participate of Sustainable Career Summit 2019 by Sells Ambassador Bangladesh.
- Participant of Daylong Career Development & Guideline Program by Leadsas Global Action in 2 time, 15th September and 30th October, 2018.
- Participant of Career Crisis and Advancement by Sharpener in 27th September, 2108.
- Participate of How To Make You Excellence by Excellence Bangladesh In 20th July, 2018.
- Participation of "12th National Red Crescent Youth Camp'12, Chittagong in 22th 25th December, 2012.
- Organized, career in marketing by Excellence Bangladesh.

REFERENCE:

• NUSRAT FATEMA

Assistant Professor Dept. Of Business Administration Stamford University Bangladesh Phone Number: +8801711244246 Email: nusrat_fatema@hotmail.com

• BENJIR ABRAR

Assistant Deputy Manager At G4S Secure Solutions Bangladesh Pvt. Ltd.

Founder at Excellence Bangladesh. Phone Number: 01689400435 Email: benjirabrar124@gmail.com

ACKNOWLEDGEMENT:

I hereby declare that submitted information is true & authentic. I have not concealed any facts or information.

(MD MAINUL ISLAM SAZIB)